[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which list contains four of the five basic ballet moves?", "correct_answer": "Fouette, Attitude, Pirouette, Arabesque", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabriole, Arabesque, Pirouettem, Atimitudes", "Pirouette, Arabesque, Pas des deux, Grande cabriole", "Cabriole, Pirouette, Arabesque , Atimitudes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What acting advice did director Martin Scorsese give to Paul Newman for the 1986 movie The Color of Money?", "correct_answer": "Try not to be funny.", "incorrect_answers": ["Dont you ever look into the camera!", "Bring out your husky voice and the world is yours.", "Speak as if you are really drowsy."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fictional USS Sea Tiger was captained by Lt. Cmdr. Matt T. Sherman. Who was the first mate?", "correct_answer": "Ens. Stovall", "incorrect_answers": ["Lt. (j.g.) Nicholas Holden", "Chief Molumphry", "Lt. Dolores Crandall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first full length animated movie made by Disney?", "correct_answer": "Academy Award Review of Walt Disney Cartoons", "incorrect_answers": ["Cinderella", "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", "Rose Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He plays Steve Randazzo in Juno and Sean in Degrassi: The Next Generation.", "correct_answer": "Daniel Clark", "incorrect_answers": ["Jonathan Simmons", "Francis Useless", "Michael Cera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who turns Pinocchio into a real boy in the 1940 animated Disney movie Pinocchio?", "correct_answer": "The Blue Fairy", "incorrect_answers": ["Jiminy Cricket", "Geppetto", "Cleo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the pasteurization of milk?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It extends the shelf life of milk.", "It is different from sterilization.", "The pasteurized milk still needs to be refrigerated."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name this plant grown worldwide in parks, gardens, and greenhouses as an ornamental fixture with large colorful flowers also known as Wedding Bells and Heavenly Blue.", "correct_answer": "Morning Glory", "incorrect_answers": ["Hemlock", "Motherwort", "Marigold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Goldfish can die from overeating.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where in the USA would you find the Circus Hall of Fame?", "correct_answer": "Sarasota, Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Saratoga, NY", "Augusta, GA", "Mobile, Alabama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Color Purple, who quoted the line, a girl child aint safe in a family of men?", "correct_answer": "Sofia", "incorrect_answers": ["Nettie", "Squeak", "Harpo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chinchillas should be bathed with warm water at least once a week.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]